Mohawk Airlines Records
Mohawk Airlines Records
- Legal files
  - 13527
    - Motion of Mohawk for Leave to File Petition for Review of Initial Decision (Box 12)
    - Answers re: Motion of Mohawk for Leave to File Petition for Review of Initial Decision (Box 12)
    - Petitions for Rehearing, Reargument and Reconsideration (Box 12)
    - Answers to Petitions for Reconsiderations (Box 12)
    - Motions for Stay (Box 12)
    - Letter Agreement TWA/Moh/AAL (Box 12)
    - Correspondence, Notes, Miscellaneous Data (Box 12)
    - News Clippings (Box 12)
    - Exhibits
      - Allegheny (Box 12)
      - American Airlines (Box 12)
      - Broome County, N.Y. and Tri-Cities Aviation Council (Box 12)
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 12)
      - Lackawanna and Luzerne Counties (Box 12)
      - New York State Department of Commerce (Box 12)
      - Williamsport Municipal Airport Authority (Box 12)
  - 16133
    - Orders (Box 13)
    - Notices (Box 13)
    - Petition for Clarification and Reconsideration of Order #E- 22133 (Box 13)
    - Outline of Issues Involved (Box 13)
    - Report of Prehearing Conference (Box 13)
    - Proposed Certificate for Route 94 (Box 13)
    - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 13)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 13)
    - Petition for Discretionary Review (Box 13)
    - Answers re: Petition for Discretionary Review (Box 13)
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
    - Miscellaneous Data (Box 13)
    - Briefs
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 13)
      - American Airlines (Box 13)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 13)
      - Erie Municipal Airport Authority (Box 13)
      - Metropolitan Development Association of Syracuse and Onondaga County (Box 13)
      - Department of Commerce State of New York (Box 13)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 13)
    - Brief to Examiner (Box 13)
    - Computer Print-Out (Box 13)
    - Testimony (Box 13)
    - Direct Exhibits, 2 volumes (Box 13)
    - Exhibits
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 13)
      - American Airlines (Box 13)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 13)
      - State of Connecticut and Hartford Chamber of Commerce (Box 13)
      - Detroit Aviation Commission (Box 13)
      - Erie Airport (Box 13)
      - Massachusetts Port of Authority (Box 13)
      - Olean, New York (Box 13)
      - Metropolitan Development Association of Syracuse (Box 13)
      - New England Council (Box 13)
      - New York State Department of Commerce (Box 13)
      - Buffalo Chamber of Commerce and Niagara Frontier Port Authority (Box 13)
    - Rebuttal Exhibits (Box 13)
  - 19097
    - Briefs
      - Braniff Airways (Box 14)
      - City of Madison (Box 14)
      - County of Milwaukee (Box 14)
      - Duluth Chamber of Commerce (Box 14)
      - Joint Central Wisconsin Cities (Box 14)
      - Minneapolis-St. Paul Metro (Box 14)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 14)
      - State of Wisconsin (Box 14)
      - Ozark Airlines (Box 14)
    - Miscellaneous Data
      - Orders (Box 14)
      - Notices (Box 14)
      - Correspondence (Box 14)
      - Petitions to Intervene (Box 14)
      - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 14)
      - Answers to Application for Show Cause Order (Box 14)
      - Petition of Western for Investigation (Box 14)
      - Petitions for Reconsideration of Order E-25805 (Box 14)
      - Motions to Consolidate (Box 14)
      - Answers to Petitions for Reconsideration and Motions to Consolidate (Box 14)
      - Statement of Issues (Box 14)
      - Motions to Clarify and Modify Issues (Box 14)
      - Answers in Support of Motion to Clarify and Modify Issues (Box 14)
      - Information Responses (Box 14)
      - Report of Prehearing Conference (Box 14)
    - Exhibits
      - Trans World Airlines (Box 14)
      - United Airlines (Box 14)
      - Western Airlines (Box 14)
      - Wisconsin Manufacturers Association (Box 14)
      - Alaska Airlines (Box 14)
      - Baltimore and Maryland Parties (Box 14)
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 15)
      - Braniff International (Box 15)
      - Brown City, Wisconsin and Green Bay Area Chamber of Commerce (Box 15)
      - Central Wisconsin Cities (Box 15)
      - City of Duluth and Duluth Area Chamber of Commerce (Box 15)
      - City of Madison and Madison Chamber of Commerce (Box 15)
      - City of Philadelphia (Box 15)
      - City of Portland (Box 15)
      - Eastern Airlines (Box 15)
      - The Flying Tiger Line (Box 15)
      - Massachusetts Port Authority (Box 15)
      - Minneapolis-St. Paul Metropolitan Airports Commission (Box 15)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 15)
      - North Central Airlines (Box 15)
      - Northeast Airlines (Box 15)
      - Northwest Airlines (Box 15)
      - Ozark Airlines (Box 16)
      - State of Washington (Box 16)
      - State of Wisconsin (Box 16)
    - Exceptions to Prehearing Conference (Box 16)
    - Petition for Review (Box 16)
    - Initial Decision (Box 16)
    - Exceptions to Initial Decision (Box 16)
    - Motion to Correct Transcript (Box 16)
    - Consolidated Cases, Application of
      - Allegheny (Box 16)
      - Eastern Airlines (Box 16)
      - City of Madison (Box 16)
      - Mohawk for Certificate of Amendment (Box 16)
      - North Central (Box 16)
      - Northwest Airlines (Box 16)
      - United (Box 16)
      - State of Wisconsin, Milwaukee County (Box 16)
      - Western Airlines (Box 16)
  - 16928
    - Briefs
      - City of Bradford, Pa. (Box 16)
      - Morgantown Chamber of Commerce (Box 16)
      - Detroit-Toronto, Erie-Toronto, 5 volumes (Box 16)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 16)
    - Orders (Box 16)
    - Notices (Box 16)
    - Proposed Statement of Issues (Box 16)
    - Motions for Consideration (Box 16)
    - Petitions for Leave to Intervene (Box 16)
    - Report of Prehearing Conference (Box 16)
    - Recommended Decision of Examiner (Box 16)
    - Miscellaneous Data (Box 16)
    - Correspondence (Box 16)
    - Application of Mohawk to Serve DTF-YYZ (#15866) (Box 16)
    - Application of Mohawk to Serve DTT-YYZ (#12608) (Box 16)
    - Application of Lake Central Airlines to Serve DTT-YYZ (#16828) (Box 16)
    - Application of North Central to Serve DTT-YYZ (#14294) (Box 16)
    - Exhibits
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 16)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 16)
      - Lake Central Airlines (Box 16)
      - North Central Airlines (Box 16)
  - 20486
    - Briefs
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 17)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 17)
      - United Airlines (Box 17)
      - Orders (Box 17)
      - Notices (Box 17)
      - Correspondence (Box 17)
      - Reference Material (Box 17)
      - Answer to Application of Mohawk (Box 17)
      - Motion to Consolidate (Box 17)
      - Answer to Motion to Consolidate (Box 17)
      - Answer to United's Revised Exhibits (Box 17)
      - Reply of Mohawk to Answers of United and Allegheny (Box 17)
      - Reply of United to Answers of Mohawk (Box 17)
      - Motion for Expedited Hearing (Box 17)
      - Motion for Leave Answer (20593) (Box 17)
      - Reply to Bureau of Operating Rights' Direct Exhibits (Box 17)
      - Motion of Mohawk to Strike the Revised Exhibits of United (Box 17)
      - Reply of United to Answer of Mohawk to Revised Exhibits of United (Box 17)
      - Initial Decision (Box 17)
      - Application of
        - Mohawk (Box 17)
        - United Air Lines (Box 17)
      - Exhibits
        - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 17)
        - Mohawk Airlines (Box 17)
  - 20411
    - Briefs
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 17)
      - Massachusetts Port Authority (Box 17)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 17)
    - Statement of Position (Box 17)
    - Statement Requesting Dismissal (Box 17)
    - Answer to Motion to Reopen the Record and Directing Submission of Further Evidence (Box 17)
    - Initial Decision (Box 17)
    - Petition for Discretionary Review (Box 17)
    - Answer to Petition for Discretionary Review (Box 17)
    - Oral Argument (Box 17)
    - Orders (Box 17)
    - Notices (Box 17)
    - Correspondence (Box 17)
    - Reference Notes (Box 17)
    - Application of Mohawk (Box 17)
    - Application Motion to Consolidate (Box 17)
    - Answer to Motion to Consolidate (Box 17)
    - Answer to Motion and Application (Box 17)
    - Reply of Mohawk to Answer of American Airlines and Allegheny Airlines (Box 17)
    - Reply of Allegheny Airlines to Answer of American Airlines and Mohawk (Box 17)
    - Answer of Mohawk to Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 17)
    - Exhibits
      - Allegheny (Box 17)
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 17)
    - Rebuttal to Exhibits American Airlines (Box 17)
  - 20294
    - Briefs
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 17)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 17)
    - Orders (Box 17)
    - Notices (Box 17)
    - Correspondence (Box 17)
    - Reference Notes (Box 17)
    - Reply of Mohawk to Answer American Airlines and United (Box 17)
    - Initial Decision (Box 17)
    - Answer of Mohawk, Allegheny and United, and Motion to Consolidate (Box 17)
    - Oral Argument (Box 18)
    - Answer to Petition for Reconsideration (Box 18)
    - Answer to Petitions for Discretionary Review (Box 18)
    - Corrections to Transcripts on Hearing (Box 18)
    - Application of Mohawk Airlines (Box 18)
    - Exhibits
      - Bureau of Operating Rights (Box 18)
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 18)
  - 13752
    - Briefs
      - Allegheny (Box 18)
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 18)
      - Mohawk (Box 18)
      - United (Box 18)
    - Orders (Box 18)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 18)
    - Petitions for Review of Initial Decision (Box 18)
  - 9977
    - Mutual Aid Investigation, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - 10281
    - Air Transport Association Investigation Sponsored by Civil Aeronautics Board, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - United States Import Duties Investigation
    - Miscellaneous, 3 folders (Box 18)
  - 14042
    - Modern Air Transport Investigation (Box 18)
  - 19209
    - Investment Tax Credit Litigation (Box 18)
  - 11022
    - California Floral Traffic Conference vs. Allegheny, 2 folders (Box 19)
  - 12285
    - Briefs
      - Allegheny Airlines (Box 19)
      - Bureau of Economic Regulation (Box 19)
      - Eastern Airlines (Box 19)
      - National Airlines (Box 19)
      - Northeast Airlines, Inc. (Box 19)
    - Orders (Box 19)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 19)
    - Prehearing Conference Report and Miscellaneous Data (Box 19)
    - Re-opened Data
      - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 19)
      - Orders (Box 19)
      - Notices (Box 19)
      - Allegheny Airlines D (Box 19)
      - Delta Airlines (Box 19)
      - Massachusetts Port Authority (Box 19)
      - National Airlines (Box 19)
      - New England Council (Box 19)
      - Northeast Airlines (Box 19)
      - United Airlines (Box 19)
  - 20116
    - Orders (Box 19)
    - Notices (Box 19)
    - Correspondence (Box 19)
    - Application of Mohawk Airlines (Box 19)
    - Answer to Application of Mohawk Airlines (Box 19)
  - 19834
    - Orders (Box 19)
    - Notices (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence Data (Box 19)
    - Mohawk Applications (Box 19)
    - Answer to Mohawk Applications (Box 19)
    - Reply of Mohawk to Trans-East Airlines (Box 19)
  - 18571
    - Notices (Box 19)
    - Correspondence (Box 19)
    - Application of Mohawk (Box 19)
    - Answer in Support of Mohawk Application (Box 19)
    - Answer of American and United (Box 19)
    - Reply of Mohawk to United Airlines and American Airlines (Box 19)
  - 19691
    - Orders (Box 19)
    - Notices (Box 19)
    - Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 19)
    - Application of Mohawk for Certificate Amended (Box 19)
    - Answer of Massachusetts Port Authority (Box 19)
    - Statements of American and Trans World Airlines (Box 19)
    - Answers of Mohawk to Motion for Consolidation (Box 19)
    - Petition for Leave to Intervene (Box 19)
    - Reply of Trans World to Answer to Motion to Consolidate (Box 19)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 19)
  - 19582
    - Briefs
      - Mohawk Airlines (Box 19)
      - United Airlines (Box 20)
    - Orders (Box 20)
    - Notices (Box 20)
    - Correspondence (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous Data (Box 20)
    - Application of Mohawk under Subpart M (Box 20)
    - Statement of American (Box 20)
    - Answer to Mohawk Application (Box 20)
    - Reply of Mohawk to American and United (Box 20)
    - Motion of Mohawk to Correct Transcript (Box 20)
    - Initial Decision of Examiner (Box 20)
    - Petitions for Discretionary Review (Box 20)
    - Answers to Petitions for Discretionary Review (Box 20)
    - Exhibits
      - United Airlines (Box 20)
  - 13355
    - American-Eastern Merger Investigation, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 11699
    - United-Capitol Merger, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - Airport Notices, 2 folders (Box 20)
  - 5828
    - Continental/United (Box 20)
  - 5827
    - Braniff/United (Box 20)
  - 3500
    - National/Pan American (Box 20)
  - 1102
    - Continental/American (Box 20)
  - 7384
    - Mohawk Permanent Certificate Case (Box 20)
  - 7456
    - Application of Mohawk for Exemption Authorizing Service (Box 20)
  - 6706
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of Certificate (Box 20)
  - 6815
    - Mohawk Application for Permanent Certificate for Route 94 (Box 20)
  - 5680
    - Mohawk Reissuance of Certificate in the Name Mohawk (Box 20)
  - 4947
    - Mohawk Certificate Renewal Case (Box 20)
  - 3386
    - Mohawk Application of Robinson Aviation for Approval to Transfer to Robinson Airlines (Box 20)
  - 1886
    - Mohawk Application of Robinson Airlines for Certificate of Public Convenience (Box 20)
  - 1702
    - Mohawk Application of Robinson Airlines for Certificate of Public Convenience (Box 20)
  - 674
    - Mohawk-Middle Atlantic Case (Box 20)
  - 17728
    - Ozark Central (Box 20)
  - 16367
    - Eastern Mackey (Box 20)
  - 5546
    - Delta/Chicago/Southern (Box 21)
  - 5376
    - Braniff/Mid-Continent (Box 21)
  - 5220
    - West Coast/Empire (Box 21)
  - 6457
    - Continental/Pioneer Acquisition (Box 21)
  - 15432
    - Mohawk, re: Service to Glens Falls Investigation (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for Temporary Suspension of service at Middletown, N.Y., 1948 (Box 21)
  - 4164
    - Application of Mohawk for Change in Service Pattern to Allow flag-stop Service, 1949 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for Suspension of Service at Middletown, N.Y., 1949 (Box 21)
  - 3961
    - Aplication of Mohawk for extension of temporary change on Route 94 re: Suspension of Auburn and Geneva, 1949 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for Suspension of Service at Middletown, N.Y., 1949 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for Extension of its Authority to Suspend temporarily at Middletown, N.Y., 1950 (Box 21)
  - 4557
    - Application of Mohawk to temporarily suspend service at Batavia, Geneva, Auburn and Oneonta, N.Y., 1950 (Box 21)
  - 4416
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary Exemption re: Utica/Rome, 1950 (Box 21)
  - 4409
    - Application of Mohawk to Suspend service at Auburn at certain times of year and omit Syracuse and Auburn on flights between Ithaca and Rochester, 1950 (Box 21)
  - 4400
    - Application of Mohawk to omit Middletown, N.Y. on all flights in excess of 2 daily round trip, 1950 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for extension of its Authority to suspend service temporarily at Middletown, N.Y., 1951 (Box 21)
  - 5025
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary exemption order Watertown, 1951 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Robinson/Wiggins Acquisition Proposal, 1951 (Box 21)
  - 5806
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption to serve Ithaca, N.Y. as an alternate interpoint to Syracuse, 1952 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for Authority to suspend service temporarily at Syracuse on Segment 3 Route 94, 1952 (Box 21)
  - 5634
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary exemption so as to permit service between Utica/Watertown, 1952 (Box 21)
  - 6353-6894
    - Application of Mohawk for a Change in service pattern (Auburn-Geneva), 1953 (Box 21)
  - 6227
    - Application of Mohawk for Order for temporary suspension of service at Pittsfield, 1953 (Box 21)
  - 6941
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of Certificate to serve Glens Falls, 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6895
    - Application of Mohawk for change in service pattern (overfly Pittsfield), 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6815
    - Application of Mohawk for permanent certificate of Route 94, 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6796
    - Application of Mohawk to Serve White Plains, 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6775
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption order (Service to Liberty/Monticello), 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6711
    - Application of Mohawk for authority by exemption or otherwise to operate an Auburn/Geneva, NY Service, 1954 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary suspension of Service to Bradford, Pa., 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6619
    - Mohawk, for amendment of certification Segment 3 terminal points BGM-DTT, 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6601
    - Application of Mohawk for authority to overfly Pittsfield, 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6488
    - Application of Mohawk to overfly Ithaca on one daily flight between Binghamton and Rochester, 1954 (Box 21)
  - 6933
    - Colonial, Application to provide service between Glens Falls-Syracuse, NY, 1954 (Box 21)
  - 7205
    - North Central, Application for exemption, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7010
    - Colonial, Application to serve White Plains, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 559
    - Application of Mohawk to serve Keene, N.H., 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7345
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption Utica/Boston, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7318
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certification, Plattsburg Service, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7317
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certification, Massena, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7316
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certification, Montreal/Plattsburg, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7315
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption Syracuse, N.Y./Newark, N.J., 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7285
    - Application of Allegheny to serve between Cincinnati, Ohio and Washington, D.C., 1955 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for order authorizing temporary suspension of American Airlines, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7188
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption Ithaca/Albany, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7143
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment Rochester/ Toronto, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7111
    - Application and Amendments of Mohawk for Amendment of Certification, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7101
    - Application of Mohawk for an exemption to serve Glens Falls, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7079
    - Application of Mohawk for a change in service pattern re: segment #5 Pittsfield, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7001
    - Application and Amendment of Mohawk re: White Plains, 1955 (Box 21)
  - 7617
    - Application of Allegheny for Approval of Change in service pattern on Segments 4 and 5 of Route 97, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 8273
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certificate non-stop service, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 8129
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption authority Utica/Albany/Boston, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 8101
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certification Cleveland/Utica, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 8100
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certification Cleveland/Utica/Syracuse, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 8099
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certificate Pittsburg/Utica/Syracuse, 1956 (Box 21)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary Suspension of Service of Auburn/Geneva, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 8075
    - Application of Mohawk for an exemption to serve Glens Falls, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 7825
    - Application of Mohawk for extension of change in service pattern re: Seg. 5 Pittsfield, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 7721
    - Application of Mohawk to overfly White Plains, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 7680
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certification (non-stop service) Elmira/Buffalo, 1956 (Box 21)
  - 8768
    - Application of Mohawk for change in service pattern for segments 1,2, and 4 (overfly Rochester, Utica, and Syracuse), 1957 (Box 22)
  - 8767
    - Application of Mohawk for non-stop service White Plains/Syracuse, 1957 (Box 22)
  - 8755
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption order to serve Ogdensburg, 1957 (Box 22)
  - 8736
    - Mohawk Application to overfly Utica and to permit non-stop between Ithaca/Albany, 1957 (Box 22)
  - 7277
    - Mail Rates, 1958 (Box 22)
  - 9349
    - Application of Mohawk for Renewal Bradford, Pa. and Liberty and Monticello, New York, 1958 (Box 22)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary suspension of service at Pittsburg, Mass., 1958 (Box 22)
  - 10670
    - Application of Mohawk to serve Springfield/Westfield through Bradley, 1959 (Box 22)
  - 10613
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment Toronto/Erie service, 1959 (Box 22)
  - 10239
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary suspension of service at Ithaca, N.Y., 1959 (Box 22)
  - 10328
    - Application and Amendment of Mohawk re: White Plains/Binghamton, 1959 (Box 22)
  - 11936
    - Application of Mohawk to overfly Erie, Pa., 1960 (Box 22)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of certificate (Buffalo/Philadelphia, Pa.), 1960 (Box 22)
  - 11495
    - Application and Amendment of Mohawk for Amendment of Certification (Washington) HPN-DCA and BUR-PLB-ALB-HPN-Phila-DCA, 1960 (Box 22)
  - 11430
    - Application by Mohawk for Exemption Syracuse/ Watertown, 1960 (Box 22)
  - [??]
    - Application of Mohawk for Authority to Suspend service temporarily at Providence, R.I., 1960 (Box 22)
  - 11298
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary suspension of service at Oneonta and Meadville, 1960 (Box 22)
  - 11202
    - Application of Allegheny for temporary exemption Hartford, Springfield, Islip and Newark, N.Y., 1960 (Box 22)
  - 11297
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption (Rochester/ Erie), 1960 (Box 22)
  - 11108
    - Application of Mohawk for amendment of certification Syracuse/New York City, 1960 (Box 22)
  - 13246
    - Allegheny Application for Amendment of Certificate for Route 97, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12846
    - Allegheny Airlines for Amendment of its certificate re: segment 7 of Route 97, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12768
    - Allegheny Application for Exemption (DTTNYC/EWR), 1961 (Box 22)
  - 13166
    - Application of Mohawk for Temporary Suspension of service at Ogdensburg, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 13141
    - Application of Mohawk for temporary Suspension of Service at Poughkeepsie, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12954
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of Certification, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12907
    - Application of Mohawk for Amendment of Certificate Segments 1 and 3 re: Erie, Buffalo, Detroit, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12872
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption (White Plains/Albany), 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12609
    - Application of Mohawk for Certificate to serve between Buffalo/Montreal via Rochester, N.Y., 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12608
    - Mohawk Application to serve DTT-YYZ, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 12491
    - American Application for Temporary suspension of Buffalo/Toronto Service, 1961 (Box 22)
  - 14232
    - Application of Lake Central to overfly Erie, Pa., 1962 (Box 22)
  - 14107
    - Application of Mohawk for removal and amendment of certificate re: Glens Falls on segment 3, 1962 (Box 22)
  - 14095
    - Application of Mohawk for renewal and amendment certificate re: segment 4, 1962 (Box 22)
  - 13629
    - Application of Mohawk for amendment of certificate to include Scranton/Wilkes Barre, 1962 (Box 22)
  - 13565
    - Application of Mohawk for change in service pattern (Non-stop Syracuse/Rochester, N.Y. and Springfield/Westfield, Mass.), 1962 (Box 22)
  - 13428
    - Application of Mohawk for exemption to overfly Erie, Pa., 1962 (Box 22)
  - 14294
    - North Central Application to serve DTT-YYZ, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14673
    - Allegheny Airlines Application for standby exemption to serve certain North Eastern Routes, 1963 (Box 22)
  - 14421